

Profile

I am a passionate customer experience architect and product designer with 7+ years experience, who enjoys it all, from researching, sketching, designing, prototyping and taking products from idea to launch. I love service design, data visualization, problem-solving and crafting digital data-driven interfaces.

Employment History

Senior product designer / CEM at DataRobot, Boston/Kyiv

July 2016 — Present

- Developing personas, journey maps and service blueprints, testing service concepts and gathering feedback
- Identify and advocate new design opportunities
- Translate technical capabilities into meaningful customer solutions that drive measurable outcomes, deliver ux solutions to clients
- Design team management, hiring, process improvement
- Help drive and build a practical and consistent data driven interface
- Work closely with functional squads from many facets of data science, engineering, product, and business to find practical solutions to design problems

Senior product designer at Newzmate

January 2016 — July 2016

- Worked on user interaction models, workflows and user interfaces
- Analyzed and selected the most impactful areas of the product and ways to improve its effectiveness through better user experience
- Executed all visual design stages from concept to final hand-off to engineering to achieve desired user experience results

UX/UI designer at Trinetix LLC

July 2015 — January 2016

- Created wireframes, mockups, interactive prototypes, mindmaps, interaction scenarios, storyboards, etc.
- Gathered and mentored the team for a special project
- Created documents for further use based on the collected information
- Collaborated with cross-disciplinary teams to concept intelligent user experiences

UX/UI designer at Akademia design house

September 2012 — July 2015

- Designed websites, application interfaces, logos, presentations, posters, books, business cards, ads, banners, flyers, t-shirts, packaging. Illustrated icons, graphics, characters, fonts. Designed, illustrated and crafted animations and motion graphics

Details

+380976883264

olha2323@gmail.com

Links

Linkedin Website

Skills

Research

Knowledgable in User Interface/ User Experience

Customer Service

Service design

Journey mapping

Consulting and Mentoring

Design Thinking

Languages

Russian

Ukraine

English

Education

pre-MBA, MIM-Kyiv Business School, Kyiv

November 2019 — Present

Digital designer, The British Higher School of Art and Design, Moscow

December 2017 — January 2018

Master of Cartography and Geodesy, Taras Shevchenko National University, Kyiv

September 2009 — June 2015

Designer, School of visual communication, Kyiv

January 2013 — January 2014